

Juan Felipe Rada

Frontend Developer

React, Redux, Tailwindcss, JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, SaSS, NGRX

OPROFILE

Developer with two years of experiences in Web development.

Passionate about creating and understanding the dynamics of the technology market, Master in Business Digital Strategy.

I am looking for a place where I can combine my programming skills with my experience from the social sciences to improve the products that the client receives.

CONTACT

Phone +55 (12) 936180526

Email radapls8@gmail.com

Website https://radapls.github.io

in LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/radapls

• Location São José dos Campos or Remote

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

English - **Professional**Portuguese - **Professional**

HOBBIES

Cooking

Sewing

AR filters

TOOLS

Intermediate professional competence

























EXPERIENCE

👂 January 2022 - Present

Frontend Developer, Wiboo Company

Creation of functionalities, maintenance of the state of the web and mobile code.

Management of Planner under the Scrum Agile model for the follow-up of tasks and deliverables. **Development tools:** TypeScript / NativeScript, Angular, Saas, NGRX, HTTP requests.

July 2020- December 2021

Social Researcher, Instituto de Estudios Interculturales

March 2019 - December 2019

Devlovery Unit Member, Secretaria de Gobierno, Alcaldia Municipal de Santiago de Cali. ■

January - June 2018

Research Assistant, Misión de Observación Electoral

March - June 2017

Research Instructor, Carrera de Ciencia Política, Pontificia Universidad Javeriana Cali. ■

August - November 2016

Research Instructor, Instituto de Estudios Interculturales

EDUCATION

0 2021-2022

Universidad ICESI - Master in Digital Business Strategy Emphasis on prototyping and user validation on the different projects. Creation of the SIGET-RB for the management of Telepacfico transportation.

2014-2019

Pontificia Universidad Javeriana Cali - Political Scientist Creation of two research seedbeds. Development of design skills